先生
中间人
第二季
第六集
翻译： 岛岛
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
我这周开始写日志了
carlo: Yeah, I started the hostility log thing this week.
翻译： silver
翻译： 噬魂
结果如何
How's that working out?
校对： silver
挺好的
Oh, yeah, good, yeah.
特效： 转轮手枪
周三的时候我遇到点麻烦
Um, had a bit of a situation Wednesday with somebody.
时间轴： 麦斯
就是在酒吧的时候有几个人盯着我看
Yeah, it was just some guy eyeballing me at the pub.
但我真的很生气
But I was getting pretty pissed
我用了之前跟你们提过的招数
and I used the stop technique, you know, we spoke about.
我超擅长的
So, yeah, I'm...I'm getting pretty good at it.
- 那挺好的  - 很好
- So that's good. - Great.
雷  你最近如何
Um, ray, how have you been?
还不错  兄弟
Yeah, good, mate.
- 是么  - 是的
- Yeah? - Yep.
你有什么想谈的吗
Is there anything you want to talk about?
没有  我挺好的
No. I'm good.
你确定  一点想说的都没有吗
Are you sure? Nothing at all?
圣诞节的时候  我把我女朋友的弟弟给打了
I beat my, uh, girlfriend's brother up over christmas.
好吧
Ok, um...
发生了什么
..What happened?
我去了她父母那边
I went round to her parents' place
我们按传统发了圣诞礼物
and, um, you know, we did the whole secret santa thing.
我女儿拿到了这根独角兽蜡烛
Me daughter got this unicorn candle,
她开心坏了
which she was pretty chuffed about.
然后我女朋友的弟弟也想要
And me girlfriend's brother decided he wanted it
等轮到他的时候  他就把蜡烛抢走了
and when it was his turn he took it off her.
所以你就给他揍了
So you assaulted him?
他太厌恶了  所以
Well, he was being a dickhead, so, you know...
- 所以你就给他揍了  - 差不多吧
- So you assaulted him? - Yeah, pretty much.
你女朋友怎么看这件事
And how did your girlfriend feel about this?
她不是我女朋友了  所以
Well, she's not my girlfriend anymore, so...
一团糟  抱歉  兄弟
- Shit. Sorry, mate.
我是想说
I mean, I...You know,
废话我就不说了
without wanting to state the obvious,
你能看出来暴力对你来说也许不是
can you see how violence is perhaps not the best way
解决纷争最好的办法吗
for you to resolve your disputes?
不  我觉得一般情况下挺好的
No, I think it generally is.
只不过  当着你女朋友的面
But, you know, just don't do it
还是别这么干了
in front of your girlfriend, you know?
这有什么好处呢
uh, what's great about it?
对你来说  这次似乎也没好处啊
It doesn't seem to have worked for you this time.
有时候有  有时候就没有  你懂吧
Yeah, well, sometimes it does, sometimes it doesn't, you know?
你能给我举个暴力有用的例子吗
Can you give me one example of violence ever working?
第二次世界大战
World war ii.
二战
- World war ii?
我们可不是靠谈判打败纳粹的
We didn't beat the nazis just by talking to 'em.
- 我们用了暴力  - 好吧
- We used violence. - Ok, sure.
时不时地
So, every now and then,
暴力有必要作为最后手段
violence is necessary as a last resort,
但对你和你女朋友的弟弟来说
but for you with your girlfriend's brother,
你打算说暴力这次是有用的吗
I mean, would you call that an example of violence working?
我是不该那么做  我这人不找借口
Look, I shouldn't have done what I did. I'm not making excuses.
但我觉得你不能说所有的暴力都是不好的
But I don't think you can say that all violence is bad.
我是说  暴力肯定有好坏之分
I mean, I think there's good violence and bad violence.
- 那好的暴力是什么  - 二战啊
- What's good violence? - World war ii.
谢了  文斯
Thanks, vince.
好了  可能到时间了
Uh, alright, maybe... It's about time.
也许我们该走了
Maybe we should leave it there.
谢了  各位  谢谢
Thank you, everyone. Thank you.
好的
Alright.
德军已经进来了
The german forces had already moved in
他们现在强行占据了修道院的废墟
and now occupied the abbey ruins in force.
给你  兄弟  肥肉可以给你吃
here you go, mate. You can have the fatty bit.
兄弟  你嚼都没嚼
Mate, you didn't even chew that.
干杯啊  宝贝
cheers, love.
- 嘿  - 你怎么样
- hey. - How you doin'?
挺好的啊  有什么新鲜事吗
Good. What's news?
没什么  你呢
Not much. What's news with you?
也没什么  你没事吧
Nothing. You ok?
没事
Yeah.
好的
Ok.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
喂
hello.
雷  我是维尼
Ray, it's vinnie.
你怎么样  兄弟
How you goin', mate?
我挺好的  哥们  你呢
I'm good, my friend. How are you?
好着呢  伙计  有什么新鲜事吗
Yeah, good, mate. What's news?
就还是那些事  你知道的
Oh, you know, same old shit in here, mate.
我就是想问候一下
Listen, I thought I'd check in
再看看你想不想有时间的时候来喝个酒
and see if you want to catch up for a beer sometime.
听起来不错啊  伙计
Yeah, sounds good, mate.
我这周太忙了
I'm pretty...Pretty busy this week.
下周末怎么样
Um, what about next weekend?
周末没问题啊   不对  不行
Sure, weekend. Oh, fuck. No, no, no, no.
我去  没法了  我得去见我的人
Fuck. No, I gotta go see my folks.
在多里戈那里有个农场
Got a farm up there in dorrigo,
我整个周末都不在
so, yeah, I'll be away all weekend.
那再往后延一周呢
Ok. What about the weekend after that, then?
延后一周   听起来不错  就这么定了如何
Weekend after. Sounds great. Let's shoot for that, eh?
可以的  我会把时间空出来的
Yeah, mate. I'll keep it free.
好的  照顾好自己啊  兄弟
Alright, you take care of yourself, brother.
- 你也是  伙计  回聊   - 好的  兄弟
- Same, mate. Talk to you soon. - Alright, mate.
再见  伙计
See you, mate.
你就打算这么走了  不管了吗  亲
you just gonna leave that there, are you, love?
- 你说什么  - 你的狗刚拉屎了
- Excuse me? - Your dog just took a shit.
- 你不打算收拾一下  - 所以呢
- Are you gonna clean it up? - So?
你就打算留着让别人踩一脚  是吧
Just gonna leave it for somebody else to stand in, are you?
要是你这么烦的话  不如你给收了吧
Well, if it bothers you so much, why don't you pick it up?
你他妈怎么不收
Why don't you fuckin' pick it up?
好吧
Oh, ok. Yeah.
不  挺好的
Nah, it's been good.
我是说  现在还是初期
I mean, it's still early days.
但他妈的  昨晚我们在床上躺着
But, fuck, last night we're lying in bed
她跟我说
and she says to me,
你和谁做爱最爽啊
"who have you had the best sex of your life with?"
我就在那躺着想啊  我去  这话让我怎么接啊
and I'm lying there thinking, "fuck, how do I answer this?"
因为她并不是我玩的最爽的
you know, because she's not the bird
那个伊人的小鸟
I've had the hottest sex with.
但我不能告诉她  我玩的最爽的一次
But I can't tell her the best sex I ever had
是和52岁的妓女在巷子里做爱  你懂吧
was with some 52-year-old hooker in an alley, you know?
我得赶紧回一句
So, I have to say something and fast,
所以我就说了  是你啊
so I say, "you!"
但因为我考虑了几秒
but because I took a second to answer,
她就问我  你为什么还要考虑一下呢
she's like, "why did you have to think about it?"
我说  我也不知道
I said, "I don't know.
你这问题搞得我措手不及
"the question kind of took me by surprise."
我告诉你啊  兄弟
I tell you, mate,
女人们问个问题可以把你吓尿了
women can ask questions that scare the shit out of you.
对的
Hmm. Hmm. True.
- 总之  这人是谁啊  - 什么谁
- So, who is this dude, anyway? - Who?
- 就这家伙  - 西蒙·吉莱斯皮
- This guy? - Oh, simon gillespie.
- 你知道吉莱斯皮家族吗  - 那个采矿的家族吗
- You know the gillespies? - The mining family?
- 对  - 好的
- Yeah. - Oh, ok.
他有什么问题
And what's his problem?
女人方面的麻烦
He's been having some lady trouble.
好的
Oh, ok.
嘿  西蒙来了
hey. Uh, simon's here.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
- 你们现在想见他吗  - 行  带他进来吧
- Do you want to see him now? - Yeah, yeah. Bring him in.
- 谢了  曼迪  - 不客气
- Thanks, mandy. - You're good.
谢了  曼迪
Oh. Thanks, mandy.
- 日安  兄弟  - 嘿  弗雷迪
- G'day, mate. - Hey, freddy.
- 还有熟人啊  - 很高兴见到你
- well, there's a familiar face. - Good to see you.
也很高兴见到你
Good to see you too.
- 已经过太久了  - 是啊
- It's been way too long. - Yes.
西蒙  这是雷
Uh, simon, this is ray.
- 嘿  雷 - 你好
- Hi, ray. - How you going, mate?
- 请坐吧  - 谢谢
- Take a seat. - Yeah, thanks.
那你不如跟雷说说你的事吧  朋友
Um, right, why don't you tell ray your story, mate?
- 开门见山啊  - 是
- Straight down to business? - Yes, yeah.
我跟一个年轻姑娘约会
Ok, well, uh, I was seeing this young lady
大概一年左右了
for about a year or so.
也不是很认真的那种吧
You know, it was nothing too serious, I guess,
反正在我看来就是玩玩的
from my perspective anyway.
然后我几周之前跟她分开了
And so I stopped seeing her a few weeks ago.
她现在就威胁要告诉我老婆
And now she's threatening to tell my wife.
还威胁说
And she's threatening
如果我不给她很多钱  她就要公布我们的事情
if I don't pay her a shitload of cash, she's gonna talk.
- 她要多少钱  - 二百万
- How much is she asking for? - 2 million.
- 牛逼  - 是啊
- Phew! Shit. - Yeah. right.
我跟她说我没那么多钱
And I told her I don't have that kind of money.
她又不听我解释
She won't listen to reason, right?
她还说要跟媒体曝光我
And she also said she's gonna go to the press
把我的丑事都说出来
and tell them all sorts of shit about me,
但这都不是真的
and none of that's true, ok?
因为我的知名度这么高  这是不可以的
'cause with my public profile, I just...I can't have that.
- 嗯  - 对吧
- No. - Right?
然后她就
So she's just, like, being, um...
完全疯狂了
She's totally off her head, you know?
那你想让我干什么呢  朋友
so, what do you want me to do, mate?
就是  你懂的
Uh, well, you know...
不行的
no, I don't.
就是让你解决掉她
I want...I want you to take care of her.
- 好的  - 嗯
- Oh, ok. - Yeah.
你意下如何
Yeah, so, what you reckon?
我考虑一下吧
Yeah, I'll have a think about it.
你要考虑一下啊
You'll have a think about it?
要多久  下周能考虑好吗  还是几天
Ok, so...Next...Next week or a few days or...?
- 几天就行 -  好的
- Yeah, couple of days. - Oh, great, great.
是这样啊  我两边都下注了
freddy: Now, this one here, I've got a bet each way.
所以如果这个赢了  就有很多钱
That...That means if it comes first, a lot of money.
如果第二或者第三  就只能赢一点钱
If it comes second or third, I'll win a little bit of money.
如果完全没赢  我就拿不到钱
If it doesn't win at all, I don't get anything,
但是除了这周很不顺的话  一般还不会手气这么差
but that never happens to me, unless I'm having a bad week.
所以这个比赛  6号比赛
Like, that's...So this... This race here, race 6...
- 你好吗 - 挺好的
- How are ya? - Good.
- 玩的开心吗  - 不错
- Having a good night? - Yeah.
什么时候能看到你跳舞啊
When are we gonna see you on the dance floor, eh?
- 我是服务员  不跳舞的  - 要是我们付钱呢
- Oh, it's not really my job. - What if we pay extra?
我不喜欢跳舞  付钱我也不跳
No, not into it. Can't pay me enough.
我可以再帮你们上点水
I'm gonna get you some water, though.
- 再来点伏特加  - 马上拿酒回来
- And some vodka. - Bring back some drinks!
卧槽  干什么啊
Fuck off! What was that?
完了
whoa, that's it!
住手  住手
Hey, hey!
你干什么啊
What are you...? Agh!
- 垃圾  - 好了  亲爱的
- Piece of shit! - Ok, ok, love.
把他们弄出去
ray: Get 'em out.
谢了
Thanks.
你可以直接用托盘打他啊
Pretty handy with that tray.
兄弟  我知道你最近不顺心
Mate, I know you're going through some shit at the moment,
但你这过分了
but fuck!
我跟你说谁打架很厉害啊
Tell you who was a good fighter.
杜兰  罗伯托·杜兰
- Durán. Roberto durán.
对  他可壮了  哥们
Yeah, yeah. Hands of stone, mate.
是啊
great, yeah.
我看过报道  梅威瑟说
Hey, I read where mayweather said
杜兰一直是他心目中排名第二的
that durán was his, uh... Number 2 on his all-time list.
那第一是谁啊
Mmm. Who was his number 1?
梅威瑟自己啊
Mayweather.
梅威瑟自己是他觉得最厉害的人里面排名第一的啊
Mayweather was number 1 on his own greatest-of-all-time list?
是啊
Yeah.
这个傻屌
oh, fuck. What a wanker.
老天爷啊
Jesus christ.
不过他记录保持的很好
He had a perfect record, though.
- 什么记录  - 50场  50场全赢
- What did he have? - 50. 50 from 50.
- 50场全赢啊  - 是啊
- 50 from 50, yeah? - Yeah.
他是27公斤组别的
He had 27 kos. Five...
- 超过别人五个重量等级  - 是吗
- Over five weight classes. - Yeah?
还拿了96年奥运会铜牌呢
'96 bronze medal at the olympics.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
你现在赚多少
What are you on?
一小时35澳币吧大概
35 bucks an hour, I think.
那你吸了什么
Yeah, and what else are you on?
就点大麻啊
Just a bit of goey.
溜冰吗
Ice?
就一点啊  兄弟
Just had a little bit, mate.
就是跟佐分开之后挺难过的
Just feeling a bit shithouse since me and zo split up,
需要提提神啊
so, needed a pick-up.
- 别抽了  - 我没事的  雷
- Get off that shit, mate. - I'll be alright, ray.
不会他么的没事的  兄弟
No, it won't be fuckin' alright, mate.
别他么吸毒了
Fuckin' get off it.
怎么  你现在还成我老板了吗
What? Are you the boss of me now, mate?
我替你担保的啊  帮你找到这份工作
Mate, I vouched for you, to get you the job.
我知道啊  我也很感激啊
Yeah, I know. And I appreciate it.
反正别给我丢脸啊
Well, you know, don't make me look bad, alright?
不会的
I won't.
你和西蒙怎么回事
what's going on with you and simon?
什么
What?
他说你勒索他
Well, he says you're trying to blackmail him.
什么
what?
我没有勒索他
I'm not trying to blackmail him!
那他为什么说你有
So why is he saying that you are, then?
我不知道啊  不是啊
Oh, I don't know. I mean, I don't know.
他说你要两百万  不然就说出去
Said you're asking for 2 million bucks to keep your mouth shut.
我只说要一个月一千澳币
look, I...I asked him for $1,000 a month
直到孩子18岁
till the baby turn... Till she turns 18.
我天啊  他
Oh, my god! Did he...
- 房子不错啊  兄弟  - 我天
- nice house, mate. - Jesus christ.
你他么吓死我了
Oh, you scared the shit out of me.
你怎么知道我住哪的
How did you know where I live?
听我说  朋友  我问过菲奥娜了
Hey, listen, mate, I talked to fiona
她现在只要25万
and I got her down to 250 grand.
- 你问过她了  - 对啊
- You...You spoke to her? - Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
25万你有的吧
You can afford 250, yeah?
有  但是吧
Uh, yeah, look, listen...
- 谢了  但是  - 嗯
- Um, thanks, yeah? - Yeah?
你不用管了  我自己处理就行了
But don't worry about it. I'll deal with that.
- 行吧 -  呢
- Oh, ok. - Yeah.
我觉得你应该给她钱  朋友
I think you should pay the money, mate.
这个
Well...
为什么要给她钱啊
..Why would I want to do that?
因为我知道她怀孕了
'cause I know she's pregnant.
行吧  好吧
Oh. Oh, ok, well, look, well...
就是
Ok, um...
就是  她跟个神经病似的
Listen, the thing is she's batshit crazy. She's...
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
你别说了  行吗
Let me stop you there, mate, ok?
48小时之内  给人家钱  好吧
Pay the money, 48 hours, ok?
- 什么 -  你听到了
- What? - You heard what I said.
我要是不给呢
w-w-what happens if I don't?
你真想试试吗
you really want to find out?
走了
Alright.
你好啊  哥们
how you going, mate?
怎么了
what's going on?
亚利克斯想知道怎么耽误了这么久
Alex wants to know what's taking so long.
如果他不乐意  可以把钱要回来的
If he's not happy, mate, he can have his money back
找别人去办事啊
and find somebody else to do the job.
-我没说他不乐意  - 嗯
- I didn't say he wasn't happy. - Mm-hm.
他只是想知道因为什么耽搁了
He just wants to know what the hold-up is.
维尼的安保很多的  兄弟
Yeah, well, vinnie's got good security, mate,
不是很容易接近的  知道吧
and he's not easy to get to, so, you know...
反正吧  他父母有个农场
anyway, his parents have got a farm.
他这周末要去那边
He's going up there this weekend,
所以我会去堵他
so I'm gonna try to get him there, so...
赶紧办完事就行了
Just get it done.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另招募长期居住海外的CC字幕录制童鞋（有酬劳）
联系QQ：864413459 注明：CC录制
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-